제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
1x01 Streaking
Sep 06, 1998 on FOX
밀어
Push,
push,
계속 밀어야 해!
come on you gotta push it!
얼마나 더?
How much longer?
10초만 더
Ten seconds.
더 세게 밀지 않으면
아무런 효과 없어!
You gotta push harder,
or it’s not gonna work!
이거 정말 멍청한 짓이야
This is so stupid!
멍청한 짓이 아니야
너도 좋아하게 될 걸?
It’s not stupid,
you’re gonna love it!
그럴 것 같지 않은데
I’m not, not gona love it.
자, 이제 시간 됐다
Okay, that’s time.
문에서 떨어져!
Step away from the door!
켈소, 넌 천재야!
Kelso, you’re a genius!
그렇지, 마술이라니까!
Yeah, well, it’s magic.
오 세상에, 이제 왔구나
목말라 죽는 줄 알았어!
Oh my god, finally,
I am so dehydrated!
자 여기 '피글리 위글리'
다이어트 크림 소다
Oh here,
Piggly-wiggly diet cream soda.
내가 '탭','프레스코','다이어트 라이트'
중에 하나 사 오랬잖아
I told you my top three choices
were Tab, Fresco or Diet Rite.
다시 말하는데, 니 껀 '피글리 위글리'
다이어트 크림소다야
Again, you get
Piggly-Wiggly diet cream soda.
그냥 물이나 마셔야겠다
Then, I’ll just have water.
뒷마당에 호스 있더라
You know,
there’s a hose in the backyard.
너희 아빠가 임시 해고되신 후로는
I’ve noticed that the pop selection
has really went downhill
음료수도 싼 걸 사다 놓는 것 같아
since your dad got laid-off.
임시 해고되신 게 아니야
He’s not laidoff,
파트타임직이 되신 것 뿐이야
he’s just part-time.
그리고 입닥쳐!
And shut up!
얘들아.. 얘들아 얘들아 얘들아..
Kids...kids kids kids
kids kids kids kids!
대통령이 오신대!
huh, the President's coming!
- 무슨 대통령이요?
- 미합중국 대통령
- What President?
- The President of the United States,
제럴드 R. 포드
제 36대..
Gerald R. Ford. The thirty-sixth,
38대..?
eighth,
40대인가? 모르겠다
하여간 대통령!
fortieth, I don’t know,
he’s the President!
포드 대통령이 우리 동네에는
왜 오시지?
Why would Ford come
to Point Place?
왜냐하면
Because.
위스콘신주 선거 운동 중에
우리 마을에서도 유세를 할 거니까
We are a whistle-stop along
his Wisconsin campaign trail.
우리 아빠가 준비했다!
My dad organized it!
얘야, 다음번에 대통령이
오시는 걸 알게 되면
Dear, the next time you know
a President is coming to town,
나한테는 좀 미리 알려 주렴
please give me a little more notice.
청소기 돌려야겠다
에릭, 여기 지하실 청소 좀 하렴
I need to vacuum.
Eric, you tidy up this basement!
파이! 파이도 만들어야지!
A pie! I gotta make a pie!
와, 대통령이 오신다니
Wow, the President’s coming.
우리가 뭘 해야할 지 알아?
You know what we should do.
- '문밀기' 또 하자
- 그래!
- That door thing again!
- Yeah!
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크, 번역 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
그래, 차는 어떠냐?
So, how’s the car?
정말 좋아요
Real good.
그 말은 내가 시킨대로 타이어 위치를
바꿔가며(rotate) 쓰고 있단 말이겠지?
편마모를 막기위해 전후좌우 위치를 교체
By real good you mean you rotated
those tires like I asked you to?
아빠, 운전할 때마다 타이어는
구르는(rotate) 것 아닌가요?
Dad, don’t they rotate
every time I drive?
말장난하는 게냐?
You’re being a smartmouth?
네
Yes,
죄송해요
and I’m sorry.
또 참치 냄비 요리야?
Tuna casserole again?
네, 그럼
자동차 보험료 내지 말고
Well, okay, how about we don’t pay
the car insurance
우리 모두 스테이크
먹는 건 어때요! / 알았어
- and we’ll all have steak!
- Alright.
상상해 보세요
포드 대통령이 여기에 오신대요
Well, just imagine,
President Ford is coming here.
여보, 마당에 있는
기름 얼룩 지워야 돼요
Uh, Red, we need to get rid of
the oil stains in the driveway.
우리집에는 안 올거야
오면 내가 엉덩이를 차 버릴 거니까
It’s not like he’s coming to our house.
And if he did, I’d kick him in the kiester.
그만해요, 어떻게 그런 말을 해요?
당신이 제랄드 포드를 뽑았잖아요
Stop it, how can you say that?
You voted for Gerald Ford.
아무도 제랄드 포드에게 투표한 적 없어
워터게이트 스캔들로 사임한 닉슨의 후임
Kitty, no one voted for Gerald Ford.
어쨌든 우리나라 대통령이란다
But, he still is our President.
쟤도 이런 얘기를 해도
될 만한 나이가 됐어
Oh, the boy’s old enough
to hear that kind of talk. Eric,
에릭, 네 직장이 하루 아침에
아무도 거들떠보지 않는곳이 돼버렸다
say that your job was sent to a plant
in quite a who-the-hell cares.
너라면 그렇게 만든 사람한테
투표를 하겠냐?
Now, are you gonna vote
for the guy that let that happen?
포드 대통령이 당신 일자리를
뺐은 게 아니에요, 닉슨 걸 뺐었지
Red, President Ford didn’t
take your job, he took Nixon’s.
에릭, 대답을 해 봐라
Eric, we’re waiting.
음...
Uh...
그게...
Well...hm,
전 모든 사람들의 정치적인 견해는
정당하며 귀기울여져야 한다고 생각해요
I believe that everyone’s political
opinion is valid and worth hearing.
그래, 완벽하구나, 에릭
Well, that’s, that’s perfect Eric.
그런 말은 미스 아메리카
선발대회에 나가서나 해라
Use that line when you run
for Miss America.
자리에 앉아라
조회를 시작하겠다
Settle down and we’ll
start the assembly.
'통조림 모으기 운동'에 관해 말하겠는데
일종의 불우이웃 돕기
Now, concerning
the canned goods drive,
윤활유는 음식이 아니다
motor oil is not a food.
미안하다만 야유해 봐야
음식이 될 수는 없다
I’m sorry it’s not and all your booing
isn’t gonna make it one.
그럼, 에헴
Now, ahem,
모두들 알다시피, 포드 대통령이
우리의 아름다운 마을에 오시게 되었다
as you all know, President Ford
will be visiting our fair city.
"성명 발표 형태의 시위"를
계획하려고 하는
And I know here’s some of you
near-to-wells out there that might be
문제아들이 몇몇
있다는 걸 알고 있다
planning some sort of quote unquote
social statement type protest.
그깟 대통령이 오는게
뭐가 그리 대수라고
I can’t believe this,
who cares if Ford is coming.
'오스카 마이어' 비엔나 소세지
차량이 마을에 왔을 때보단 낫네
It’s better than when the Oscar Mayers
Weenie mobile drove through.
그 차는 멈추지도 않았어
They didn’t even stop!
그저 속도를 낮추고 핫도그 모양
호루라기 한뭉치나 던져주고 갔지
They just slowed down and threw
a bunch of hotdog whistles at us.
아가씨 둘이 거시기 모양 차를 타고
다니면서 니가 불어대던 걸 나눠줬지
Two girls in a phallic RV, driving
around handing out things you blow…
대단한 나라야
What a great country.
그러니 내가 하는 말을 잘 들어라
신사, 숙녀
So let me tell you another thing,
mister or misses,
못된 것들아
punk.
시위는 해봐야 소용없다
Protesting accomplishes nothing…
오 물론, 너희들이 성인임을 입증하거나
멋지게 보일 기회로 생각할 수 있겠으나
Oh sure, you might see a chance
to prove your manhood or
show you’re cool…
이 분은 이 나라의
대통령이시란 말이다
But this is our President,
대통령 말이야, 망할!
our President, darn it!
그러니 어떤 장난도 안된다, 알겠나?
So no shenanigans, you hear me?
만약 그런 짓을 할 생각이라면
지금 당장 집에나 가 버려라!
If that’s your kind of attitude,
you might just go home right now!
그러니까 포드 대통령은
정오에 도착하게 될 겁니다
So President Ford
should be arriving at noon.
와, 양념 계란이다!
Oh man, deviled eggs.
Ah...are these for anybody?
주인있는 거 아니죠?
안녕, 아빠
- Hi, daddy. Hi, Mister Pinciotti.
- Hi.
- 안녕하세요, 핀씨오티씨
- 잘 있었니?
안녕, 아가
어른들끼리 할 얘기가 있으니
Hi kitten, oh, we’re talking
about adult stuff here.
친구랑 네 방으로 올라가렴
Why don’t you and your friend
head up to your room?
대통령 유세 집회에서
가장 중요한 것은
Now, the most important part
of our presidential rally is
마을 주민의 Q&A 순서일 거요
the town’s people Q&A section.
이해를 돕기 위해 한 말씀 드리면
Uh...just so everyone’s clear,
Q는 질문을 뜻하고
A는 대답을 말하는 거지요
the Q stand for question,
the A for answer.
나머지는 자네가 다 얘기하게
All yours, Jack.
평범한 주민이 마이크 앞에 나가서
This is where normal folks
step up to the microphone
대통령에게 질문을 하는 겁니다
and ask the President questions,
알다시피 가장 중요한 것은
적당한 사람을 고르는 것일텐데
now you the important thing is
to chose the right person, you know.
노동자 계층이면서
평균적인 시민으로
A working class guy,
your average Joe.
우리가 낙오자라고 부르는
사람을 뽑아야 될 것 같군요
Huh, I guess someone you
and I would call a loser.
그래서 당연히 자네를 생각했지
So of course I thought of you.
우리는 자네가 대통령에게
질의를 했으면 좋겠어
We’d like you to ask
President Ford a question.
그래 어떻게 하겠나?
So, what do you say to that?
내 대답은 "고맙지만 싫어!"일세
그리고 내 렌치 돌려주게
I say no thank you and I want
my crescent wrench back.
제가 할게요
I’ll do it.
아뇨, 아뇨, 가서 계속
파이나 구우세요
No, no, you keep
working on your pies.
상상해보게 레드, 보잘 것 없는 사내인
자네가 미국 최고의 권력자에게
Just imagine Red, you, the little guy
get to have your opinions heard
본인의 의견을
말할 수 있는 기회야
by the most powerful man in America.
이 기회를 잡으라구
Take advantage of this opportunity!
- 불 꺼라
- 죄송해요
- Turn that light off!
- Sorry.
얘들아, 우린 부패한 선거 제도에 대한
거부를 보여주기 위해 뭔가 해야 돼
Look guys, we gotta
do something that says
we'll not pay an homage
to a corrupt electoral system.
그래, 유혈 쿠데타를 하는 거야
I know, a bloody coup!
그것도 좋지만
좀 더 멋진 걸 찾아야 돼
That’s good, but we’re
looking for something great.
우리를 낳아주신 아버지들이
자랑스러워 하실 것으로, 알았어?
Something that will make our founding
fathers proud, man, you know?
스트리킹 하자! / 빙고!
- Let’s streak!
- Bingo!
항상 해보고 싶었어. 군중들 속을
다 벗고 달리는 거야
I’ve always wanted to do that. Just run
buck naked through a sea of people.
자유롭게 흔들고 다니는거야
Be free and shake it around!
좋아, 할 사람?
All right, who’s in?
사람들이 몽둥이랑 각목을
들고 쫓아오지 않을까?
Will people be chasing us
with tortures and pointy sticks?
아니
- No.
그럼 나도 할래!
- Then, I am in!
좋았어!
Great!
에릭, 너도 할래?
Eric, are you in?
난 스트리킹은...
Okay...streaking...I'm...
오해하진 말아줘
벗는 건 자신 있지만
Don’t get me wrong,
I’m completely pro nudity,
아빠가 날 죽일 거고
난 죽는 건 반대거든
but I think my dad might kill me
and I’m anti being killed.
야
Hey,
이런 멍청한 짓을 하는데
그정도 위험요소가 없다면
if there wasn’t some huge downside
to doing something this stupid,
할만한 가치가 있겠냐, 응?
it wouldn’t be worth
doing, you know?
좋은 지적이야
Good point.
오, 오, 게다가 정말 멋진
슬로건도 쓸 수 있어
Oh, oh, and I could write
some really great slogan like
엉덩이에 '난 짭새(fuzz)가 싫어요!'
라고 쓰는 거야
'I hate the fuzz!’ on my ass!
엉덩이에 난 솜털(fuzz)이 싫거든
면도해 버리면 되잖아
If you hate the fuzz on your ass,
why don't you just shave it off?
정말 멋지지?
Pretty snazzy, uh?
좋아 보이네요, 아빠
Looking good, dad.
네가 입을 것도 있단다
I got one for you, too.
우리가 그걸 입고
대동령을 만나는 거야
We’re gonna wear them
to meet the President!
아니, 안 돼요!
No, no way!
얘야, 대단한 볼거리를 놓치는 거야
Honey, you...you’re missing
the big picture.
다른 점프수트를 가져올테니
한번 봐라
Let me go get the other
jumpsuits, you’ll see.
엄마, 왜 이러시는 건데요?
Mom, why are you doing this?
얘야, 아빠를 기쁘게 하려고
싫어도 하는 일들이 많이 있단다
Honey, there are lots of things
I do to make your father happy
that I don’t really like.
- 엄마, 으웩!
- 깜짝이야!
- MOM, eww!
- Oh, my!
아니, 이건 맘에 들어
No, not that. I love that.
내 말은 낚시같은 거 말이야
I meant like fishing.
봐라, 우리가 나란히 서 있으면
성조기가 되는거지
See, when we stand together,
we’re the American flag.
줄무늬 점프수트는
입지 않을 거예요 / 오
I’m not wearing
a stripped jumpsuit. / Oh.
오, 오, 얘야
넌 파란 부분이란다
Oh, no, honey,
you’re the field of blue.
됐어요
Bye now.
하지만 도나
너도 가족의 일원이잖아
But Donna, you’re
part of the family!
오, 이런, 마음이 아프군
Oh, my, this hurts.
여보쇼
Yello.
밥, 좋은 소식일세
Good news, Bob.
생각해 봤는데, 내가 포드에게
질문을 하기로 결심했네
I’ve been thinking about it and I’ve
decided I will ask Ford a question.
오 이런, 레드
좋은 소식이군
Oh geez Red, this is good news.
당장에 이 소식을 전해야 겠네
And I could sure
use it right about now.
그래, 도움이 돼서 기쁘군
Yeah, well, glad I could help.
제대로 된 질문을 해야지
Oh, I’m gonna ask him
a question all right.
기똥차게 제대로 된 걸로
And it’s gonna be
a damn good one.
여보?
Red?
걱정하지 마
Now, don't worry,
난 단지 대체 이 경제를 어떻게
해결할 거냐고 물을 거니까
I’m simply gonna ask him how
the hell he’s gonna fix this economy!
오, 여보, 그 사람이 그걸
어떻게 알겠어요, 대통령이잖아요!
Oh, honey, he wouldn’t know that,
he’s the President!
이 음식이 다해서 45센트라니
믿기지가 않아
All this food for 45 cents.
It is unbelievable.
알 거 같아
Oh, I see.
야 포먼
So Forman,
집회는 오늘이야
어떻게 할거야?
the rally’s tonight man,
what’s your decision?
그래, 스트리킹 할거야?
Yeah, are you gonna streak or not?
강제로 시키지 마
Don’t pressure him.
아냐, 생각해 봤는데..
No, I’ve been doing
some thinking, and
- 할거야
- 좋았어! / 알았어
- I’m in.
- Yeah! / Alright.
너희들은 바보 떨거지로 보일 거야
Well, you’re gonna
look like a bunch of idiots.
벌거벗은 바보 떨거지야!
A bunch of naked idiots.
고맙구나, 켈소
Thanks Kelso.
있잖아, 우린 이걸 비밀로 해야 돼
이 자리에서 새 나가면 안 돼
Look, we must keep this quiet,
it can’t go beyond this table.
아빠가 아시게 되면
날 벽에다 못박아 버리실 거야
If my father finds out what we've
planed, he will nail me to the wall.
왜 모두 한 테이블에
모여 있는 거야, 응?
Why are you all sitting
on one set of the table? Huh?
자, 대통령용 파이 나갑니다
Okay now, make way
for my presidential pies.
좀 봐요, 체리, 모크애플, 블루베리
저기는 빨간색, 흰색, 파란색
See, cherry, mock-apple, blueberry.
See that. Red, white and blue.
파이로 미국 사랑의 시작을
표현해 봤어요
It’s like the beginning
to Love American style in pie!
봐요, 좀 봐요
당신, 안 보고 있잖아요
Look, look it. See, honey,
you’re not looking.
그래, 파이네
Yeah, pie.
아빠, 핀씨오티씨가 이걸
아빠한테 드리라고 하던데요
Hey dad, Mr. Pinciotti
wanted me to give you this.
이게 뭐냐?
What is it?
아빠가 포드 대통령께
할 질문이래요
That’s your question
for President Ford.
하지만 대통령에게 할 질문은
내가 지금 생각하는 중인데
But I’m working on my question
for President Ford.
그러게요, 근데 이건
위원회에서 만든 거래요
Right, well, this is the one
the committee made up for you.
가장 마음에 들었던
퍼레이드는 무엇입니까?
What has been
your favorite parade?
이게 뭐야!
This is asinine!
"메이시" 요
뉴욕의 메이시 추수감사절 퍼레이드
Macy’s.
- 오, 문제 낸 게 아니에요
- 그렇지
- Oh, no contest.
- Right.
트렌치 코드 좀 빌려주실래요?
Can I borrow your trench coat?
난 내가 원하는 건 뭐든지
대통령에게 물어볼 수 있어
I can ask the President
any damn thing I want.
그건 내 권리야!
It’s my right!
난 위원회의 꼭두각시가
되진 않을 거다
I’m not gonna be a puppet
for Bob’s committee.
알았어요, 제가 잘 처리하고
최대한 빨리 답변을 가져올게요
Right, I’ll take good care of it
and I’ll bring it back
as soon as I possibly can.
얘야, 그냥 코트나 가지고 가거라
Honey, just take the coat and leave.
아니다, 에릭
No, Eric,
남자라면 당당히 일어서서
말해야 한다
a man has to stand up,
and be heard.
나한테서 모든 것을 빼앗아 가는데
조용히 앉아있을 수 만은 없어
I will not sit quietly by while every
thing is taken away from me.
내 일자리도 빼앗고
They took my job,
안정된 생활도 빼앗더니
my stability,
이제는 자유발언의
권리마저 빼앗으려고 하는구나
now they wanna take away
my right to free-speech.
토요타 자동차는 아직 있잖아요
마일리지도 많아요
You still have the Toyota,
it gets great mileage.
내가 어릴 적에 알았던
미국은 어디 있는거야?
Where’s the America
that I knew as a boy?
어디에?
Where?
하느님, 말해보십쇼
어디 있습니까?
You tell me, dear God, where?
전 지금 이 순간
이 방에 있기 정말 싫어요
Okay, I relly hate being
in this room right now.
좋아, 대통령이 여기에서
연설을 시작하면
Okay, when the President
starts his speech here,
내가 핫도그 호루라기를 불면
그때 하는거야
I’ll blow my Oscar Meyer
whistle, and we go.
엉덩이에 '난 짭새가 싫어요'
라고 썼니? / 응
Did you write 'I hate
the fuzz' on your butt?
Yeah.
도나, 어, 립스틱 돌려줄게
Donna, uh, here’s your lipstick back.
그냥 가져
Keep it.
가면은 구했어?
Hey, you’ve got the masks?
그래, 스누피 가면 3개하고
닉슨 가면 1개
Yeah, I’ve got three Snoopies
and one Nixon.
찜!
Not it!
이런, 페즈, 너 그런 말은
어떻게 알았어?
Damn, Fez, how did you know
how to do that?
우리나라에서 만든 말이야
My country invented "not it".
그럼, 우리 이제 갈까?
Right, so, can we go already?
우리 똘똘이 풀고 싶어서
근질거리거든
I’m itching to release the hound here!
해보자!
It’s go time.
오, 얘들 좀 보게
Oh, well, now look at you guys.
콜롬보 형사 놀이라도 하는 거니?
What is it with you young people
and Colombo?
안녕히 계세요
Bye.
잘 가라
넌 안 가니?
Aren’t you going, Donna?
네, 아빠가 정말 이상한
점프수트를 입히려고 해요
No, my dad’s gonna make me
wear this really queer jumpsuit.
그런 옷을 입을 수나 있을지
모르겠어요
I don’t know if I can do it.
너무 부끄러워요
It’s just too embarrassing.
그거 아니? 도나
You know Donna,
우리 할머니는 스웨덴에서 오셔서
억양이 아주 이상하셨지
my grandmother came from Sweden,
and she had this thick thick accent
그게 난 한없이 부끄러웠단다
and it embarrassed me to no end.
그래서, 고등학교 졸업식에
오시지 말라고 했어
Well, I asked her not to come
to my high school graduation
내 친구들이 할머니가
말하는 걸 듣는 게 싫었거든
'cause I didn’t want
my friends to hear her talk.
그래서 안 오셨지
And she didn’t come.
16년 후에, 통풍에 걸리셨고 돌아가셨지
엄지발가락에 생기는 관절염
Sixteen years later,
she got the gout and died.
이제 알겠니?
You see?
아뇨
No.
가족이란 다 부끄럽단다
All families are embarrassing.
부끄럽지 않다면 그땐
그들이 죽은 다음이겠지
And if they’re not embarrassing,
then they’re dead.
사람들 사이에 섞여야 돼, 알았지?
Alright, try to blend in, huh.
- 야, 내 여자친구한테 집적대는 거야?
- 마이클, 그런 거 아냐
- Hey, you’re hitting on my girlfriend?
- Michael, he’s not.
- 형씨, 좋아, 한 판 붙어 볼래?
- 좋아. 해보자고!
- Hey man. Fine, you wanna go?
- Come on. Let's go!
너 운 좋은 줄 알어!
벗지만 않았어도!
You are so lucky! I’m naked, pal!
여기에 별모양 파란 부분이
올 예정이었어요
There’s supposed to be
a blue field of stars there.
오 얘야
Oh honey.
이제 우리가 앞뒤로 흔들거리면
Now if we just start to
sway back and forth,
바람에 나부끼는 깃발 같을거야
it’ll look like the flag is
waving in the wind.
세상에!
Oh God!
저기, 트렌치 코트
입은 사람이 또 있어
Hey, there’s another guy
in a trench coat.
저 사람도 스트리킹 할 건가봐
I bet he’s a streaker too.
아니야 페즈
저 사람은 경호원이야
No Fez, he’s with secret service.
저 사람은?
How about that man?
경호원이야
Yeah, Secret service.
저 사람도?
And that man.
맞어
Yeah.
- 개 데리고 있는 저 사람도?
- 응 / 맞아
- And that man with the dog?
- Aha./ Yeah.
아, 개가 우리를 보고 있어
이리와 멍멍아
Oh, the dog is looking at us.
Come here boy.
하지마, 페즈!
No Fez!
오! 이런, 이제 생각났다
Oh! Man, I just thought of something.
뭐가?
What?
우리 트렌치 코트는 어떻게 해?
What are we going to do
with our trench coats?
우리가 벗어던지고 나면
가지러 돌아 올 수 없잖아
I mean after we rip them off,
we can't come back here and get 'em.
제기랄!
Oh, shucks!
오, 모두 내 실수야
이렇게 하자
Oh God, this is all my fault!
You know what?
내가 코트를 챙길테니까
너희들이 스트리킹을 해
I’ll hold the coats, you guys streak.
고맙네
Thanks.
나도 지금 생각난 게 있어
I just thought of something, too.
우리는 벗었는데
여기는 개가 많잖아!
We’re naked,
and there’s a lot of dogs here!
우리 그냥 앉는 게 좋겠다
Maybe we should just sit down.
- 동감이야
- 나도 / 나도
- I’m in.
- Me, too. / Me, too.
그래
Okay.
신사숙녀 여러분
Ladies and Gentlemen,
미합중국 대통령
제럴드 R. 포드 입니다
the President of the United States
of America, Gerald R. Ford!
야, 여기 숨어서 뭐해...
Hey, what are you doing
hiding over…
알았어
Oh, okay.
물러서! 난 성조기야
Back off. I am a flag.
스트리킹 할 거니?
Are you gonna streak?
아니, 투표를 했는데 만장일치로
안 하기로 했어. 우린 모두 겁쟁이야
No, we took a vote and it’s unanimous.
We’re all very chicken.
너무 아깝다
너 벗은 거 본 지도 한참됐는데
That’s too bad. It’s been a while
since I’ve seen you naked.
나 벗은 거 본 적
한번도 없잖아
You’ve never seen me naked.
수 천번도 더 봤지!
Like a zillion times!
우리 어렸을 때 너 맨날 발가벗고
동네를 뛰어다녔잖아
When we were kids and you were always
running around the neighborhood
naked screaming Wee-Wee Pee-Pee!
'위위 피피' 하면서 아기들 오줌 누일때 쓰는 말
이제는 질의 순서를
진행하겠습니다
Now it’s time for the Q&A
portion of our program.
먼저, 레드 포먼씨를 소개합니다
First up, I’d like
to introduce Red Forman.
훌륭한 두 자녀의 아버지이며
Red is a father of
two wonderful children
직장에서 파트타임으로
내려 앉았는데도
and how he’s managed
to keep them clothed and fed
어떻게든 자식들은 먹여 살리는 거 보면
나보다 나은 사람입니다
while being cut back to halftime
at the plant is beyond me.
하지만 그는 자신의 불행을
대통령 탓으로 돌리지 않습니다
Now he doesn’t blame
the President for his misfortune,
아뇨, 그는 자책할 뿐입니다
no sir, he only blames himself.
레드 포먼을 소개합니다
I give you Red Forman.
음...
Um...
헤헴.. 대통령 각하?
Hem...Mr. President...
저는...
I uh…
어서, 레드
Come on, Red.
너네 아빠 엄청 쫀다
Your dad is bombing.
위위 피피!
Wee-wee Pee-pee,
Wee-wee Pee-pee!
제리, 제 질문은 이겁니다
Hey Gerry, here’s my question:
대체 어떻게 닉슨을
사면할 수가 있소?
How the hell could
you pardon Nixon?
왔냐?
Hey son.
네
Hi dad.
오늘 잘 하셨어요
Hey um, good job
at the rally today.
나쁘진 않았지...
처음에는 말문이 막혔지만
Not bad… I kinda stumbled
there at the start, but
제대로 한 방 먹였지
I think I nailed him with a good one.
어쨌든 꽤 멋졌어요
Well anyway it was,
it was pretty cool.
그래, 때때로 남자는 옳다고
생각하는 대로 해야 한다
Yeah well, sometimes a man’s
gotta do what he thinks is right.
네, 전 그만 자야겠어요
Yeah, I’m, I’m gonna call it a night.
그래, 아들아. 잘 자라
Alright son. Good night.
안녕히 주무세요
Good night dad.
다음에는 검은 양말은 신지 마라
멍청해 보인다
Oh, and next time, don’t wear
black socks. You look like an ass.
그 사람들 어떻게 널 못 잡았을까?
How could they not catch you?
아무도 벌거벗은 남자한테
달려들고 싶지 않았겠지
I guess no one wants
to tackle a naked guy.
그랬을 거야
So true.
근데 너...
아무 것도 못 봤지? 그치?
Hey, you didn’t, you didn’t
see anything, did you?
그래
No,
음, 어쩌면 아주 쬐금 봤나?
well, maybe just a bit.
But not, not the bit.
쬐그만 걸 봤다는 게 아니라...
잠깐, 쬐금은 무슨 뜻이야?
Wait, what do you mean bit?
번역수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
최종수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24